Thank you for watching!
Good morning.
Today, you need to be good at acting.
Good at acting?
I'm going to ask you to act in a famous
scene of a drama.
Wow.
That's great.
I haven't thought about whether you
know the drama or not.
I see.
If you don't know, please do your best.
Wow.
The living generation is different.
I think so.
I know the drama of the Sengoku period.
Sengoku period?
There is a box of paper with the famous
scene of the drama that you will act.
You will decide the order of drawing a
lottery.
The winner will announce the winner.
If you think you need to act as the
opponent, please offer it.
I see.
That's all for the explanation of the
rules.
Yes.
Let's play the king's rock-paper-
scissors.
King?
Let's do it.
Please subscribe to the channel.
I'm 99% sure.
I'm going to win.
Don't go anywhere.
I'll do my best.
The game is about to start.
The game has started.
I'm curious.
Hurry up.
Please check the contents.
I knew it.
To be continued.
The main character of the story is a
sun.
Are you OK with one person?
Can I offer?
Please.
The title of the story is,
I wrote,
Roar to the sun.
So,
Sun.
This person is a sun.
The main character roared to the sun,
So, I wrote,
Roar to the sun.
I think so.
The sun didn't let it rain,
So, I wrote,
Roar to the sun.
I think it's a person who is about to
fall.
I see.
I'll do it.
Don't laugh.
What is this?
Cut!
No!
That's all.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Who wants to do it?
Do you want to do it?
Yes!
Have you ever seen this?
Have you?
Yes, I have.
I'm going to do it alone.
I'm going to split up.
I'm going to be a man.
My mom said,
Hurry up and eat.
If I do that, I'll be the one who eats.
I'm going to eat.
Then, the second person, please.
Hey, eat properly.
Hurry up and eat.
Do it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
We're done eating.
Let's do the next one.
I'm still eating!
I did it!
I've never seen someone who's been
doing this for 6 years.
I was surprised.
You're good at it!
I'm good at it!
next
, but SAMATU
Music doesn't
I act
Song citizens
Both
Bar
body
n
I'm sorry.
There are so many people.
It's a police station.
Thank you.
I will solve this case.
I will bet on my grandpa.
I will win.
That's great.
Is it right?
Yes, it is.
The result is...
Yay!
This
and
the
first
voodoo
is
I'm not sure if it's me.
I'm fine with it.
Do you have a name?
Misako.
I'm a girl.
The fourth person, please.
Misako, are you going to die?
No, Misako.
Misako, I want to be with you.
No, no.
Why? Why are you going to die, Misako?
I'm not going to die!
She's crying.
I thought Misako was going to die.
That's amazing.
I'm going to solve this problem.
I'm going to be a little girl.
I'm going to die.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Question
I want someone to take care me
But there separated also
Who want to take care me?
I'm going to buy a house.
You can't buy a house.
What do you buy?
Where is the money?
It's impossible.
Buy it.
I'm poor.
It's impossible.
Cut.
I'm poor.
Nice to meet you.
Please subscribe.
Yeah!
Let's move on.
Please.
Shizu-chan, you can go first.
I'm OK.
Oh!
What?
Cool!
OK, I'll go.
Action!
The incident doesn't happen in the
conference room.
It happens on the spot.
Wow!
What was that?
That was cool!
I can't move with that kind of
connection.
Next.
Me.
I think I need a partner because I'm a
man.
I'm a woman.
She's a famous actress.
I'm not talking about a man.
I'm talking about someone I like.
A woman?
Please.
Where is she?
She...
She?
I'm a little mean, but I like being
kind.
You're mean.
Can't you just be kind?
It's boring to be kind.
Then I'll make you enjoy it more.
I won't make you regret it.
So...
I can't.
That's good.
She did it.
She's cool.
I'm sorry. I was a little mean.
I made a mistake.
I was a little mean at first.
That's the problem.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Please subscribe to the channel
and I try to see 2
Should I choose
Mr. Tsuke and Mr. Gack,
such the
more I try to
Genma
feel good
house
that all
in
Mr. Tsuke
shade
to
Ready, action!
Oh no!
Help!
Wait!
Can't you see this door?
Please subscribe to our channel!
Cut!
Thank you!
It was a good experience!
It's me!
I'm funny like a Galileo.
Let's make a line.
Can I write a line?
It's a line, so it's good to have a
sense of rhythm.
Galileo is a cosine tangent.
This is a cosine tangent.
So, let's write a line.
Cosine.
It's really funny.
We can just do this.
Action!
Sine.
Cosine.
Tangent.
It's really funny.
Action!
OK!
I've seen this.
It's called sine cosine tangent.
That's right.
Yeah.
The answer is...
Yeah!
Let's play the game twice.
One rabbit is under the roof.
If a rabbit is lonely, it will die.
Someone who gave up breeding.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
Let's play again.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Hey, who's the keeper today?
Why? Why didn't you feed the rabbits?
I forgot.
You have to feed them every day. Why
did you leave them?
Because I wanted to play.
Rabbits die when they are lonely.
Let's see.
Wow.
Great.
I was surprised.
The last one.
School Wars.
I will punch you.
That's cool.
But I can't.
Do we say it together?
Oh, we do.
I'm scared if you say it in a sudden.
Let's do it.
Action.
I'll give you a camera.
Hide!
What is this?
It was fun.
I enjoyed it.
We also did it twice.
We like it.
There are many series.
I want to change the taste.
If the taste is decided, we will do it
again.
That's cool.
If the taste is decided, we will do it
again.
Please add it next time.
If the taste is decided, we will do it
again.
The blue part is mine.
The title is mine.
That's all for today.
Thank you for watching.
See you next week.
Bye bye.
Is that all?
We have to do it again.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Thank you for watching.